<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.7.4">
  <compounddef id="indexpage" kind="page">
    <compoundname>index</compoundname>
    <title>Janrain Engage Android</title>
    <detaileddescription>
<para><ulink url="http://rpxnow.com/docs/android">The Janrain Engage for Android SDK</ulink> makes it easy to include third party authentication and social publishing in your Android app. This library includes the same key features as Janrain Engage for the web, as well as additional features created specifically for the mobile platform. With as few as three lines of code, you can authenticate your users with their accounts on Google, Yahoo!, Facebook, etc., and they can immediately publish their activities to multiple social networks, including Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, MySpace, and Yahoo, through one simple interface.</para><para>Beyond authentication and social sharing, the latest release of the Engage for Android SDK now allows mobile apps to:<itemizedlist>
<listitem><para>Share content, activities, game scores or invitations via Email or SMS</para></listitem><listitem><para>Track popularity and click through rates on various links included in the shared email message with automatic URL shortening for up to 5 URLs</para></listitem><listitem><para>Provide an additional level of security with forced re-authentication when users are about to make a purchase or conduct a sensitive transaction</para></listitem><listitem><para>Configure and maintain separate lists of providers for mobile and web apps</para></listitem></itemizedlist>
</para><para>Before you begin, you need to have created a <ulink url="https://rpxnow.com/signup_createapp_plus">Janrain Engage application</ulink>, which you can do on <ulink url="http://rpxnow.com">http://rpxnow.com</ulink></para><para>For an overview of how the library works and how you can take advantage of the library&apos;s features, please see the <ulink url="http://rpxnow.com/docs/android#user_experience">&quot;Overview&quot;</ulink> section of our documentation.</para><para>To begin using the SDK, please see the <ulink url="http://rpxnow.com/docs/android#quick">&quot;Quick Start Guide&quot;</ulink>.</para><para>For more detailed documentation of the library&apos;s API, you can use the <ulink url="http://rpxnow.com/docs/android_api/annotated.html">&quot;JREngage API&quot;</ulink> documentation. </para>    </detaileddescription>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
